// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "대구대학교 공식 캐릭터 이름은?",
    answer: "두두",
    options: [
      "뽀로로",
      "다다",
      "두두",
      "도라에몽"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "대구대학교 본관은 어디에 있나요?",
    answer: "경산시",
    options: [
      "부산광역시",
      "대구광역시",
      "경산시",
      "서울특별시"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "대구대학교 학과중 아닌것은?",
    answer: "KFC학과",
    options: [
      "특수교육과",
      "언어치료학과",
      "직업재활학과",
      "KFC학과"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "대구대학교 창립일은 언제 인가요?",
    answer: "1956년 5월 1일",
    options: [
      "2002년 2월 4일",
      "1997년 4월 17일",
      "1950년 6월 25일",
      "1956년 5월 1일"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "대구대학교 크기는 전국에서 몇번째 인가요?",
    answer: "3번째",
    options: [
      "1번째",
      "2번째",
      "3번째",
      "4번째"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "대구대학교의 기숙사가 아닌것은?",
  answer: "드림기숙사",
  options: [
    "비호생활관",
    "향토생활관",
    "행복기숙사",
    "드림기숙사"
  ]
},{
  numb: 7,
  question: "다움중 대구대학교의 도서관은?",
  answer: "창파도서관",
  options: [
    "문파도서관",
    "창솔도서관",
    "창파도서관",
    "창미도서관"
  ]
},{
  numb: 8,
  question: "다움 중 본교의 교화로 알맞은 것은?",
  answer: "백일홍",
  options: [
    "개나리",
    "백일홍",
    "장미",
    "진달래"
  ]
},{
  numb: 9,
  question: "다움 중 본교에 없는 시설은?",
  answer: "볼링장",
  options: [
    "골프장",
    "수영장",
    "볼링장",
    "헬스장"
  ]
},{
  numb: 10,
  question: "다움 중 본교에 없는 광장은?",
  answer: "비호광장",
  options: [
    "사랑광장",
    "비호광장",
    "자유광장",
    "빛광장"
  ]
},
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];